

Interests

Football

Skills

Microsoft Word

Microsoft Excel

Abdallah Mohamed

Sales Representative

Profile

With more than five years working in the field of sales; I was able to discover what is going on in the soul of every consumer, and I knew the correct way in which I could convince each person of what they see from their own perspective, which is of course a skill that cannot be overlooked when working in this field, and therefore; I have sought to join your work in order to contribute to the company's sales department being a pioneer and distinguished person.

Experience

Free Business

2017 - 2019

Free business in the field of buying and selling

Patrol

Branch Manager | 2019 - 2021

Branch Manager of Patrol Garment Company

Education

Bachelor of Laws

Menofia University, Shebin Elkom | 2017 - 2020 Description of the education/course.

Contact

- Shebin Elkom
- 201061046829
- ✓ abdallamo1411@gmail.com